声明：本字幕由YYeTs人人影视字幕组原创翻译制作
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎登录人人影视论坛交流 下载 在线观看 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：爱爱  paradise  小帝  许愿
时间轴：leolou456  不爱
字幕总监制：何何  后期： 梁良
这是最后的两个蛋了
These are the last two eggs.
从我书架上拿来的?
From my own bookshelf?
-帮你打发一下时间  -这本我都看过了
Help you pass the time. I've already read it.
看第二遍可以让你温故知新
You might catch something you missed the second time around.
你为什么要把我从关押室转到这里来?
Why did you move me from the rec room down here?
我想让你呆在我眼皮底下
I wanted you under my own roof.
你把其他人关在哪儿?  Miles 是叫这个名字吧
Where are you keeping your other prisoner? miles, is it?
看来你不想告诉我
Oh, you don't want to share.
事实上  Ben  我倒是希望你能告诉我点什么
Actually, I was hoping you would share, ben,
既然你都说了在船上有个内线
Seeing as you claim to have a spy on his ship.
John  我真同情你
I feel for you, john.
发自内心的同情你
I really do.
你不断的碰壁
You keep hitting dead ends.
找不到想要的答案
You couldn't find the cabin.
你没法感受到Jacob
You can't make contact with jacob.
你如此绝望的想知道下一步该怎么做
You're so desperate to figure out what to do next,
你甚至现在都问到我头上来了
You're even asking me for help.
既然这样  还是像从前那样
So here we are, just like old times...
你把我换到另外的房间去
Except I'm locked in a different room.
不然你只会更郁闷
And you're more lost than you ever were.
我知道你有什么企图
I know what you're trying to do.
没用的
It's not gonna work.
不错嘛  John  你变机灵了
Excellent, john. you're evolving.
早饭吃完了吧
Done with your breakfast?
那是怎么回事?
What's that all about?
谁知道呢  Locke就这样的
Who knows? it's locke.
女士们  早上好
Mornin', ladies.
早上好
Good morning.
早安
Mornin'.
咖啡闻起来很香啊
Mmm, coffee smells good.
好吧  我去给你倒一杯
Well... why don't I go make you a cup?
感觉有点怪吧  不是吗
Kinda weird, ain't it?
悠闲的坐在前廊  一杯杯喝咖啡
Sittin' on porches, drinking coffee out of mugs.
我找到一些你可以穿的衣服
Anyway, I found some clothes about your size.
挂在一个衣橱里面的
Hung 'em in a closet.
那么在我赶走Hugo之后
So after I kick out hugo...
James  我不会和你一起住的
I'm not moving in with you, james.
好吧  那你干嘛留下来
Well... then why did you stay?
这不关你的事
That's none of your business.
你是不是有个什么秘密计划?
Oh, you got a secret agenda, huh?
要是你帮Jack做内线的话
Well, if you're spying for jack-
-我没有替任何人做内线  -那你干嘛不告诉我...
I'm not spying for anyone. so why don't you tell me-
因为我不相信你
Because I don't trust you.
看来是跟怀孕的事有关
This is about the pregnancy thing.
James...
怎么了?
Yeah?
回去吧
Go home.
好吧
Okay, fine.
那就待会见了
See you later, then.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
这里有后门吗
Is there a back entrance?
是有  但是你要从前门
Yeah, but you're going in the front door
抬着头走进去  好吗
With your head held high, okay?
好的  可以
Yeah. okay.
我们走吧
Let's do this.
Kate  你为什么这么做
Why'd you do it, kate?
请让个道
Coming through.
伙计们  现在我们不会发表任何意见
Hey, folks, we're not making any statements
或者回答任何问题  抱歉
Or answering any questions right now. excuse us.
以下将对Katherine Anne Austen提起公诉
The people against katherine anne austen.
主审法官Arthur Galzethron
The honorable arthur galzethron presiding.
法庭监守宣读诉状
The bailiff will read the counts.
被告请起立
Will the defendant please rise?
Katherine Anne Austen
Katherine anne austen,
你被起诉诈骗
You are charged with fraud,
纵火  袭击联邦官员
Arson, assault on a federal officer,
持械伤人
Assault with a deadly weapon,
大窃盗罪(指所窃财物超过一定价值的盗窃)
Grand larceny,
偷盗汽车
Grand theft auto
以及一级谋杀罪
And murder in the first degree.
Austen女士  你怎么辩解
Miss austen, how do you plead?
我不认罪
Not guilty.
鉴于以上情况  现在听取保释辩论
Thus entered. I'll now hear argument on bail.
法官大人  我们要求
Your honor, we are requesting
被告在候审期间
That the defendant be remanded into custody
不得保释出狱
For the duration of the trial.
法官大人  我的委托人可以随时被提审
Your honor, my client's been free pending arraignment.
现在怎么突然她就有了逃跑的可能了?
Now suddenly she's a flight risk?
她绝没有逃走的可能
she's the very definition of a flight risk.
全美国人民都认得出她这张脸
She has one of the most recognizable faces in america.
-她还能跑到哪里去呢?   -Austen女士  基于你的前科
Where is she going to run? miss austen, based on your prior history,
我倾向于民意
I'm inclined to agree with the people.
你须得接受联邦关押候审
You are hereby remanded into federal custody for the duration of your trial.
-法官大人,我的.. -法庭监守  请将被告带去关押
your honor, my- Bailiff, please take the defendant into custody.
抱歉
Sorry.
爱伯克奇（新墨西哥州第一大城市）
Al-bur... quer-que?
太热了
Too hot.
纽约?
New york?
人太多了
Too many people.
比首尔人还多?
More than Seoul?
首尔有什么不好的了?
What's wrong with Seoul?
Sun  我们随时可以离开这个岛
sun, we're going to leave this island any moment now
我是为了和你一起
I learn english... for you...
呆在美国才学英语的
To live... in... america.
我想要...
I want...
让我的孩子在韩国自己家里长大
To raise my baby at home. in Korea
你是指我们的孩子
You mean our baby
快看哪  Jack
Hey, look! jack!
Jack!
你还好吧
You're okay!
你们好啊
Hey, man.
这两位是Charlotte和Dan
This is, uh, charlotte and dan.
你好
Hey.
Sayid和Desmond已经坐直升飞机
Their helicopter
回到他们的船上去了
Already took sayid and desmond back to their freighter.
他们可以安排
They can make arrangements
我们大家离开这个岛
To get all of us off this island.
Kate在哪里
Where's kate?
她和Locke在一起
She stayed with locke.
Kate  你好
Hello, kate.
那是血吗
Is that blood?
我刚杀了只鸡
I just... killed a chicken.
我能为你做什么吗
What can I do for ya?
我想和Miles谈谈  你把他关在哪儿了
I wanna talk to miles. where you keeping him?
你干嘛要跟他谈谈
Why do you need to talk to him?
是我的一点私事
Well, that's personal.
-不行  -你凭什么说行或不行
No. and what gives you the right to decide whether or not--
Kate  可能你认为这里是民主管理的
You may think this is a democracy, kate,
也许Jack处理事情的方法让你有这种感觉
Because of the way jack ran things.
但是在我这里没有什么民主
But this is not a democracy.
那我猜你是想独裁吧
Then I guess that makes it a dictatorship.
要是我是个独裁者
If I was a dictator,
我会一枪毙了你  然后该干嘛干嘛去
I would just shoot you and go about my day.
饿了的话6点会开饭
Dinner's at 6:00 if you're hungry.
Hurley
Hey, hurley!
等等
Wait.
-你是把那个给Miles吗  -是的
You bringing that to miles? yeah.
-Locke让我来送  -好啊  那家伙让我不大爽
Yeah, locke asked me to do it. cool. that dude creeps me out.
-他还是关在休闲厅对吗  -不  我把他转移到船屋...
He's still in the rec room, right? no, I moved him to the boathouse that..
你是在故意套我的话吧
You just totally scooby-doo'd me, didn't you?
对不起
Sorry.
-你不会放他走的  对吧  -不  不会  我保证
You're not gonna let him go, are ya? no. no, I promise.
不要告诉Locke我让你去的
Just don't tell locke it was me.
那个阿拉伯人也把你换来了?
So the arab traded you, too, huh?
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
什么意思
Excuse me?
你知道我是什么人吗
Do you know who I am?
你知道我做过什么吗
Do you know what I did?
你做过什么
What did you do?
回答我的问题
Answer the question.
好吧
Okay.
我会给你想要的答案
I'll tell you what you want to know,
但你得先为我做点事情
But you gotta do something for me first.
我不会放你走的
I'm not letting you go.
我不想被放走  这就是我想来的地方
I don't want to be let go. I am exactly where I want to be.
我要的是...
What I want...
和一个人
Is one minute...
待上一会儿
Of someone's time.
你把他带给我
You bring him to me,
我就告诉你所有关于你的事情
And I will tell you everything I know about you.
你要的是谁
Who?
你觉得还能是谁呢
Who do you think?
你还好吧
You okay?
我还好
Yeah, I'm fine.
听着  地区检察官要亲自做这个案子
Listen, the d.a.'s decided to try this case herself,
这就意味着他们会全力以赴
Which means they're gonna do the full court press,
我们就得想法庭外调解
And we need to start talking about cutting a deal.
怎么个调解
What kind of deal?
老实说  据我最乐观的估计
Honestly, my best guess,
可能她会判你个15年
I'd say she'll take a 15-year sentence,
你服刑到第7年可以申请假释
And you serve seven.
没门
No way.
Kate 如果你的案子庭审的话
If you go to trial, kate,
每项罪名都会让你关上个20年
You're looking at 20 years on each count,
-更别说你那项谋杀罪名就得判个终身监禁 -不行
Not to mention a life sentence on the murder charge. no.
Kate  你都向你妈亲口供认
Kate, you confessed to your mother
是你杀害了你父亲
That you killed your father,
现在她成了有力的人证
And now she's their star witness.
那你来告诉我  我该怎么办
So you tell me- what am I supposed to do?
-我要怎么才能赢这场官司  -带我上法庭吧
How am I supposed to win this thing? put me on the stand.
然后期望地区检察官放你一马?  不可能的
And take a chance with the d. a. crossing you? no.
依我之见  我们可以博一把
Way I see it, we've got one shot at this.
-是什么  -我们在身份上做文章
What's that? we make it about character,
不去纠结于你做过或没做过这些
Not about what you did or didn't do,
而在于你是什么人
But about who you are.
什么意思  我是什么人?
What do you mean, who I am?
我想让他出席法庭
I want him in the courtroom.
-绝对不行  -Kate  我们需要他去
Absolutely not. we need him, kate.
这会带来极大的同情关注
It'll generate tremendous sympathy.
Duncan  听我说  你不能把他带过去
Duncan, listen to me. you are not bringing him in here.
好吧,你想这么做这案子,关于我的身份？可以
All right, you wanna make this about me, about my character? Fine
但你就是不能利用我儿子
But you are not using my son.
或许我们还可以试着
Maybe we should try a number
打一打除了那船以外的号码  比如说911
Other than the boat, like... 9-1-1.
怎么回事?
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
就是跟那船的联系出了点问题
We're just having some trouble getting ahold of their boat.
你还没有Sayid的消息吗  你说他们昨天就走了
You haven't heard from sayid? you said they left yesterday.
我确定他们应该没事
And I'm sure they're fine.
万一Locke是对的呢
What if locke was right?
万一这些人真的是来伤害我们的?
What if these people are here to hurt us?
Locke做事情没理智的
Locke has no idea what he's doing.
那为什么Kate留在他那边?
Then why is kate with him?
你确定他把Ben关在地下室吗
You sure he's got ben in his basement?
恩  我看到Rousseau昨晚把他带过去的
Uh-huh. I saw rousseau take him in there last night.
-Locke出去过吗   -没有  他整天在里面烧菜弄饭
Does locke ever go out? no. he's been in there cooking all day.
他邀请我们大家去晚餐
He invited us all over for dinner.
你能帮我带一下Aaron吗
Oh, can you get aaron for me?
就是把他抱起来  轻轻的摇摇拍拍
Just pick him up and rock him a little bit.
我有点不大擅长和婴儿打交道
Yeah, I'm just... not very good with babies.
我不想把他弄得更不舒服
I wouldn't want him to get more upset.
好吧  我来抱他
Here, I got him.
没事的
It's okay.
小宝贝  到这儿来
Here we go, muffin.
对了  抱住你了
Yeah. there we go.
你真会带他
You're so good with him.
是吗
What?
我从没想过
Just the last thing
自己能够当个好妈妈
I ever thought I'd be good at is being a mum.
你知道  有时你得试着去做
You know, you should try it sometime.
Aaron  别哭了  亲爱的
Hey, aaron. come on, sweetie.
请起身
Please rise.
现在开庭  请就座
Court is now in session. please be seated.
不要怪我  好吗
Don't fire me, okay?
什么
What?
一开始你就败仗阵来  我必须这样做
We got killed in the opening. I had to do this.
被告有证人没有
Does the defense have a witness?
是的  有  法官大人
Yes, we do, your honor.
被告传召Jack Shephard医生
The defense calls dr. jack shephard
到证人席
To the witness stand.
法官大人  基于他们的关系
Your honor, I'd like to renew my objection to this witness
我重申反对传唤这为证人
On the basis of relevance.
反对无效
And I'm going to renew my overruling of your objection.
你们知道  该证人
You are to be aware that this witness
在被告被控告有罪后
Did not meet the defendant
才认识的
Until after the alleged crimes she is being charged with.
他只能视为被告的品德信誉见证人
He's to be viewed as a character witness only.
请继续
Proceed.
请举起右手
Please raise your right hand.
你能向上帝发誓你所说的话
Do you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
-全部是事实吗?  -是的
And nothing but the truth so help you god? yes.
Shephard医生
Dr. shephard...
你能告诉陪审团
Could you please tell the ladies and gentlemen of the jury-
你们之中谁没有读过报纸
If there are any of you who don't read newspapers
上过网或看过电视...
Or the internet or watch television...
你是怎样认识被告的
How you met the defendant?
在2004年9月22日
On september 22, 2004,
Kate...
我和Austen小姐
Miss austen and i
是大洋815航班的乘客
Were both passengers on oceanic flight 815,
该飞机坠毁在南太平洋一个岛上
Which crash-landed on an island in the south pacific.
你知道Austen小姐是一名逃亡者吗?
Were you aware that miss austen was a fugitive
知道她由一名美国执行官押送
Being transported by a united states marshal
-乘座飞机到洛杉矶接受审讯吗?  -是的  我知道
On that flight to los angeles for trial? I did learn that eventually, yes.
是从美国执行官那得知的吗?
From the u.s. marshal?
不是  执行官在坠毁中死了
No, the marshal died in the crash.
我从来没有和他说过话
Uh, I never spoke to him.
Austen告诉我的
Miss austen told me.
-你是否问过她她到底有罪没有?  -没有
Did you ever ask her if she was guilty? no. never.
似乎还是个合情理的问题  为什么
Well, it seems like a reasonable question. why not?
我觉得肯定是有一些误会
I just assumed that there'd been some kind of mistake.
你为什么这样认为
And why would you think that?
飞机坠毁后只有我们八人生还
Only eight of us survived the crash.
我们掉在水里
We landed in the water.
我伤得很重
I was hurt pretty badly.
事实上  要不是她的话
In fact, if it weren't for her,
我肯定上不了岸
I would have never made it to the shore.
她照顾我们  照顾我们所有人
She took care of me. she took care of all of us.
她给我们急救
She--she gave us first aid,
给我们找水和食物  建庇护所
Water, found food, made shelter.
她试图救另外两个  但是他们没有...
She tried to save the other two, but they didn't--
别说了
Stop.
Austen女士  请坐下
Miss austen, please sit down.
这和...和这些事没关系
This has nothing to do with... with anything.
这是我的审判
This is my trial,
我不想他说与此无关的事
And I don't want him to say anything else.
好了  我没有问题了  法官大人
It's fine. I have no more questions, your honor.
Dunbrook女士
Miss dunbrook,
到你发问
Your witness.
这真让人感动  Shephard医生
That was very moving, dr. shephard.
我只问你一个问题
I only have one question for you--
-你爱被告吗  -反对
Do you love the defendant? objection.
Forrester  是你开了先河
You opened this door, mr. forrester.
我允许问这个问题
I'm going to allow it.
Shephard医生
Dr. shephard?
你爱Austen女士吗
Do you love miss austen?
不爱
No.
不再爱了
Not anymore.
那么  你想看什么
So... what do you want to watch--
世外桃源或撒旦死亡记?
Xanadu or "satan's doom"?
我在看书
I'm reading.
把那玩意儿关小点  妈的
Turn that thing down, damn it.
抱歉
Sorry.
-嘿  -我能进来吗
Hey. can I come in?
当然可以
Sure.
-我敢肯定你认识我的室友  -你好  Hurley
I believe you know my roommate. hi, hurley.
你好  Kate
Hey, kate.
你眼睛进东西了吗  Hugo
Got somethin' in your eye, hugo?
我们不如到厨房谈吧
Why don't we talk in the kitchen?
我知道尽管是在盒子里  但是
I know it's in a box, but, uh...
真的是他妈的好酒
It's pretty damn good wine.
我尝过了
I tested it.
和Claire住在一起感觉怎样
So how's the life at casa de claire?
Aaron是不是吵得你整夜睡不着?
Baby aaron keeping you up all night?
-不  他睡得很熟  -那很好啊
No. no, he's a good sleeper. good for you.
你真行  雀斑女
You are terrible at this, freckles.
你说过你不是为我而留下来的
You already said you didn't stay behind for me.
至少你得够女人味
So at least be woman enough
来告诉我你要利用我做什么
To tell me you wanna use me for somethin'.
我想你帮我
I wanna use you for somethin'.
瞧  没那么难吧
See? wasn't that hard.
干什么
For what?
把Ben弄出来
For ben.
我想你帮我把Ben弄出来
I want you to help me bust him out.
想玩玩西洋双陆棋吗
Wanna play some backgammon?
好啊
You're on.
我不确定自己的所作所为
Do you think I know what I'm doing?
你...
Do you...
后悔跟我一起到这儿?
Regret following me out here,
还是担心我们下一步该怎么走
Or are ya worried about what we should do next?
如果我在那岸边的话我会更担心
I'd be a lot more worried if I was sittin' on that beach.
剩下的那些人  他们在谈论什么
And the rest of the group-- what are they saying?
我想他们在谈论...(羊叫声)
I think they're saying, "baa."
关于绵羊的  这是件好事
That's the nice thing about sheep.
他们是这样预言的
They're predictable.
但是我不敢肯定Kate也这样想
But I ain't so sure about kate.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我要你发誓你不会伤害她
I need your word you ain't gonna do nothin' to her.
-我为什么要伤害她  -你向我保证  John
Why would I do anything to her? just give me your word, john.
你知道吗  算了
You know what? forget it.
不  好吧
No, no. no. all right.
我向你保证
You have my word.
一个小时前她找到我
She came to me about an hour ago,
要我帮助她
Said she wanted my help
把Ben从地下室弄出来
Busting ben out of your basement.
为什么
Why?
她和那家伙谈过了...
She talked to that guy...
就是从货船来的李小龙  你关着的那个
Bruce lee from the freighter- the guy you got locked up.
-他叫她把Ben带去和他谈谈  -不  不可能
He told her to bring ben down to him for a chat. no, that's impossible.
-她连Miles在哪都不知道  -什么
She doesn't even know where miles is. what?
他在去船坞的船库里
the boathouse down by the dock?
只要Hugo知道  大家都会知道
If hugo knows, everybody knows.
你确定吗
Are you sure about this?
是的  我确定
Yeah, I'm sure.
你带那玩意儿要上哪去
Whoa, whoa, whoa. where you going with that?
不管Miles要对Ben说什么
Whatever miles has to say to ben,
他都可以和我说
He can say to me.
婊子养的
Son of a bitch.
快点
Come on.
一分钟  快点
You got one minute. go.
能不能单独谈
How about some privacy?
55秒
55 seconds.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
你知道我为谁工作
You know who I work for?
对
Yes.
那么你也知道他花了很多时间和精力
Then you know he's put a lot of time and energy
来找你
Into finding you.
现在我找到你了
So now I found you,
我可以告诉他你到底在哪儿
And I can tell him exactly where you are.
或者我可以撒谎
Or I can lie
说你已经死了
And tell him you were already dead.
如果你愿给我320万
And I'd be willing to do that
我很乐意说你死了
For $3.2 million.
你安排这次会面就是为了敲诈我吗?
You've arranged this meeting so you could blackmail me?
如果你认为是敲诈  那就是吧
It's extortion, if you wanna get technical.
320万  为什么不说330万或340万
3.2? well, why not 3.3 or 3.4?
是什么让你觉得我有那么多钱
What makes you think I have access to that kind of money?
不要以为我是他们中一员
Do not treat me like I'm one of them,
不要认为我不知道你是谁和你的能力
Like I don't know who you are and what you can do.
你的朋友Charlotte来见过我
Your friend charlotte has seen me.
她知道我还活着  我会照顾好Charlotte
She knows I'm alive. I'll take care of charlotte.
你就只管担心给我凑钱吧
You just worry about getting me the money.
你有两天时间
You have two days.
我目前的情形有点糟糕
My present situation is a little bit restricted.
-可不可以在缓点  -好
Can that be amended? okay.
-一星期  我要现金  -时间到了
One week, in cash. time's up.
想都别想
Don't even think about--
我说时间到了
I said time's up!
你这样让我激动
Ooh, this is hot.
你已见到他了  现在我要我的答案
You got your meeting. now I want my answer.
当你呼叫货船时我们就知道你的名字了
We got your name when you called the freighter.
当然  我们知道你的一切
Of course, we know about you
而且其他人的名字也在815名单上  也证实了你的名字
And everybody else on the 815 manifest. then prove it.
你叫Katherine Anne Austen
Your name is katherine anne austen.
因谋杀  敲诈  纵火而被逮捕
You're wanted for murder, fraud, arson,
其他事我也记不清了
A whole bunch of other stuff I can't remember.
你是个逃亡者  在澳大利亚被抓
You're a fugitive, got caught in australia,
联邦调查人员把你逮捕归案
And the feds are bringing you back.
是的  我们都知道
So, yeah, we know.
如果我是你  我就会呆在这岛上
If I were you, I'd stay right here on the island.
这样谁也不知道  别人可能以为你在坠毁中死了
Who knows? maybe you didn't survive the crash.
走吧
Come on.
快回去  Kate
Go back to your house, kate.
-John  这和你没关系  -滚回去  Kate!
John, this has nothing to do with you- go back to your house, kate!
你还好吗?
Hey. you okay?
我睡不着
I couldn't sleep.
我们是要花点时间去习惯睡这床
Yeah. the beds take a little getting used to.
我没吵醒Aaron吧?
I didn't wake aaron, did i?
没有  Aaron是在这岛上出生的
No, aaron was born on this island.
他不管怎样也能睡着
He can sleep through anything.
John?
你来有事吗?
What are you doing?
我想和Kate单独呆会儿
I'd like a... a moment alone with kate.
可以吗  Claire
Would you excuse us, please, claire?
没事
It's okay.
我不想知道你为什么这样做
I don't need to know why you did what you did.
Kate  我只想知道他们说了什么
Kate, I just need to know what they said to each other.
Miles告诉Ben
Miles told ben that he would lie
他会向他船上的老板撒谎
To the people he works for on the boat,
只要拿到320万  他就告诉他们Ben已经死了
Tell them that ben was dead, for $3.2 million.
John  我很抱歉
Listen, john, I'm sorry.
我问过你他在哪
I asked you where he was-
你不能再呆在这儿了
You're not welcome here anymore.
我希望你明早就走
I want you gone by morning.
我想你们俩该单独谈谈
I worked it out so you two can have a few minutes of privacy.
我不想和她谈
i don't need any privacy.
你应该和她谈谈  Kate
You need to talk to her, kate.
我会在外面
I'll be outside.
你好  Katherine
Hello, katherine.
Shephard医生说的是真的吗?
Was it true, what he said?
他说你是个英雄
Dr. shephard-- that you're a hero.
你为什么不理我?
Why won't you talk to me?
因为,妈妈上次你病了,我试着和你交谈
Because, mom, the last time I tried to talk to you, when you got sick,
我冒险去看你
When I risked my life to see you,
-你却大叫救命还打电话给警察  -求你了
You screamed for help and called the police. please.
我不想和你吵  Katherine
I don't want to fight with you, katherine.
你为什么来这?
Why are you here?
因为...
Because...
我...
I...
一切都变了
It all changed
我那时以为你已经死了
When I thought you were dead.
医生说我只能活六个月
My doctors have given me six months to live
在过去四年里
For the last four years.
我不知道自己还能活多久
I don't know how long I'm going to last.
我来是想告诉你  我...
I came here to tell you that i...
我不想指证你
I don't want to testify against you.
那就不要
Then don't.
我想见见我孙子
I want to see my grandson.
你来这和我谈条件?
You came here to make a deal?
我只是想见见他
I just wanna meet him.
我不想你接近他
I don't want you anywhere near him.
我们说完了
We're finished.
我们说完了!
We're finished!
嘿  雀斑女
Oh, hey, freckles.
你还好吧?
You okay?
对不起  我不能坐视不管
Look, I'm sorry I couldn't do nothin'.
我想让他觉得你也耍了我
I wanted him to think that you fooled me, too.
他相信我们俩
No sense in him not trusting both of us.
他让我在明天前离开
He wants me gone by tomorrow.
什么  他...赶你走?
What, he... banished you?
呃  我不会赶你走
Well, I un-banish you.
你可以呆在...
You can stay right...
这儿
Here.
这是我的屋子
This is my house.
好吧  是我和Montezuma的房间
Okay,me and montezuma's house.
你一定会没事的
You're gonna be all right.
我会保护你
I'll keep you safe.
时间到  好了  告诉我
Time. okay,tell me.
你都记得什么牌?
What do you remember?
好  呃  方块Q
Okay,uh,queen of diamonds.
然后  我们有...梅花...
Then we... six...
的...
Of...
六  不好意思
Clubs. sorry.
我们还有十...
And we have the red 10 of...
红心  对吧?
Hearts, maybe?
对了两个
It's two out of three.
还不错
It's not bad.
有进步
It's progress.
就三张牌  Charlotte
Three cards,charlotte.
算是进步吗?
Is that progress? hey.
呼叫了一天了  你的船上怎么没人应答?
Been calling your boat all day. why isn't anyone answering?
我们俩在这  我们怎么知道?
We're here. how should we know?
如果没人应答  那他们可能已经...  -你不会是想告诉我
If they're not answering, then they're probably-- now are you telling me
你的船上只有一条通信线路吧?
There is only one line on that boat?
还有一个通信号码
There is another number
是为紧急情况准备的
That we're only supposed to use in emergencies.
这就是紧急情况
It's an emergency.
放在免提上
Put it on speaker.
喂?
Yeah?
Regina  我是Charlotte
Regina, it's charlotte.
-你怎么用这个号打过来?  -Minkowski没接
Why are you calling me on this number? minkowski wasn't answering.
岛上的人想和他们的朋友通话
The people on the island want to talk to their friends,
从而确定他们安全
Make sure they're all right.
什么...朋友?
What...friends?
他们昨晚离开了这里
They left last night.
Frank开着直升机接走了他们
Frank took 'em up in the helicopter.
什么意思  开直升机接他们?
What do you mean, they took off?
我以为直升机一直在你们那
I thought the helicopter was with you.
早安
Morning.
听着  我不知道你在干嘛
Listen, I don't know what you think you're doing,
你只是在浪费你的时间  张嘴
But you're wasting your time. open your mouth.
张嘴  大一点
Open your mouth. wide.
呃...
Uh...
别出声  咬住  咬住
Don't talk. bite down. bite down.
我觉得我那天把你捆起来的时候
I realize that when I tied you up in here the other day,
没能好好介绍自己
I made the mistake of failing to introduce myself.
我叫John Locke
My name is john locke,
维护这个岛的安宁
And I'm responsible for the well-being of this island.
最终  Miles  你会告诉我你是谁
Eventually, miles, you're gonna tell me who you are
还会告诉我船上那些人的情况
And you're gonna tell me about the people on the boat
还有你们为什么对Ben那么感兴趣
And you're gonna tell me why you're so interested in ben.
但是现在
In the meantime, however,
你的把嘴闭紧
You're gonna keep your mouth shut.
昨天我学到
I learned something yesterday.
如果没有惩罚  规矩就没用
No use having rules if there's no punishment for breaking 'em.
你咬住触发器就不会有事
You'll be fine if you bite down on the trigger.
享受你的早餐吧
Enjoy your breakfast.
等等  等会  慢点  慢一些
Wait a minute. wait a minute. just--slow down. slow.
来吧
Oh, come on.
又不是没这么干过
It's not like we ain't never done it before.
昨晚我们没离开可真好
Yeah,I'm cool we didn't go all the way last night.
知道了  你很难过
I get it. you were sad.
但我想说
But, I mean,
你又怎么能抗拒那句
How can you resist after that whole,
让我保护你呢？
I'll keep you safe thing?
不是   Sawyer...只是...
No. sawyer... just...
只是什么?
What?
只是...算了
Just... forget it.
好吧
Oh, right.
你仍然觉得你可能怀孕了
You still think you might be pregnant.
我不担心
I'm not worried.
而且我没怀孕
And I'm not pregnant.
你确定?
Are you sure?
是的  是真的
Yeah, I'm sure.
哈哈!
Ha ha!
我是说...
I mean...
如果那样会是最糟的吗?
Would it have been the worst thing in the world?
会啊!当然  那将是世界上最糟糕的事
Yes! yes,it would've been the worst thing in the world.
我们有了孩子该怎么办?
What would we have done with a baby?
我要回海滩去
I'm going back to the beach.
海滩?怎么  因为这个你就要走?
Beach? what, you're leavin' because of this?
就这样了?你跟我上床
That's that? you crawl up in my bed one second,
-紧接着  你就要  -再见
The next, you're just-- good-bye.
别拿我出气  Kate
Don't make this about me, kate.
你并不是比我更想要个孩子
You didn't want a baby any more than I did.
你不过是想找个理由离开
You're just lookin' for some excuse to split,
现在你找到了一个
And now you got one.
那么好吧  雀斑女
Well,that's all right,freckles.
我不跟你吵
I ain't gonna hold it against ya.
我只会呆在这  在我舒适的床上
I'm just gonna sit right here in my comfy bed,
因为只消大概一周
Because in about a week,
你就会找个理由和Jack闹翻
You'll find some reason to get pissed at jack
然后回到我身边
And bounce right back to me.
好吧
Good. all right.
回医院去
Go back to the hospital,
查出她的医生是谁
Find out which doctor she's visiting.
- 我想让你查出她在哪  - Dunbrook小姐
- I want you to find out where she - miss dunbrook.
可以继续了吗？
Are the people ready to proceed?
法官大人  我们想近前谈话
May we approach the bench, your honor?
好吧
Oh. please.
不幸的是  法官大人
Unfortunately, your honor,
我们的主要证人  Diane Jansen  被告的母亲
Our chief witness, diane jansen, the mother of the defendant,
由于某些健康原因不能出庭作证
Is unable to testify because of medical reasons.
你需要多长时间?
How long will you need?
现在我还说不准
I can't say right now.
我将休庭至午饭时
What I'll do is grant a recess for lunch,
但在我们开庭时请你准备好继续你的案子
But be prepared to proceed with your case after we return.
现在休庭
This court is now in recess.
起立
All rise.
我们得谈谈
We have to talk.
我的主要证人昨天和她的女儿交谈
My key witness spoke to her daughter yesterday,
而现在她却退却了
And now she's got cold feet.
装的挺像  那我们就商量商量
Quit posturing, and let's get to it.
你的提议是什么?
What are you offering?
四年监禁
Four years in.
不能有监禁
No jail time.
Kate Austen是全世界的英雄
Kate austen is a worldwide hero
她在坠机事件中救了五条命
Who saved five other peoples' lives after a plane crash
在一个废弃的岛上差点饿死
And nearly starved to death on a deserted island,
而在这些之后  你把她告上法庭
And after all that, you put this woman on trial
仅因为她想把她妈妈从施虐狂丈夫手中救出
For rescuing her mother from an abusive husband.
如果你认为陪审团会给她监禁
If you think that jury is gonna give her actual time, then...
你也太天真了  Melissa
You must have a hell of a closing, melissa.
好吧
All right.
监禁时间不变  加上十年缓刑期
Time served, plus 10 years' probation
-而且必须保证她不能离开美国  -那有什么关系?
And agreement that she does not leave the state. what does that matter?
-她能去任何地...  -我接受
She can go anyw-- I'll take it.
-不  等等  Kate  -给我个协议  我会签
No. wait, kate-- give me something to sign, and I'll sign it,
然后我走出后门
And then I walk out the back door.
我只是...
I just...
我只是想这一切结束
I just want this to be over.
好吧
I can do that.
十年缓刑  你呆在这
10 years' probation, and you stay put.
我有个小孩
I have a child.
我哪都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
嘿
Hey.
你怎么知道我会来这?
How did you know I'd be here?
你的律师给了我提示
Your lawyer gave me the heads-up.
他欠我的
He owed me one.
谢谢...
Thank you...
你说了你做的
For saying what you did.
不客气
You're welcome.
你知道  Jack  我已经听过你说那个故事好多遍了
You know, jack, I've heard you say that story so many times,
我觉得你开始相信了
I'm starting to think you believe it.
我只想-
I just--
我只想告诉你  我在那所说的...
I just wanted to tell you that what I said in there...
都不是我的本意
I didn't mean it.
你能跟我来?
You wanna follow me?
顺便来我家做客吗?
Come by for a visit?
呃...
Uh...
我..我得去医院
I... I actually have to get over to the hospital,
不过  你我也许
But, um, maybe you and i
可以一起喝杯咖啡？
Could grab some coffee together or something?
我知道你为什么不想看到孩子  Jack
I know why you don't wanna see the baby, jack.
但直到你想
But until you do,
直到你想见...
Until you want to...
就不会有...你我去喝咖啡之类的话了
There's no... you and me going for coffee.
但是...
But, um...
如果你改变主意
If at any time you change your mind,
过来看看我们
Come and see us.
好
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
再见
Bye.
有人吗?
Hello?
Kate!很高兴你回来
Kate! I'm so glad you're back.
他特别想你
Mmm. he missed you so much.
-你有没有管着他别看电视?  -当然
Did you keep him away from the tv? absolutely.
我刚把他放下打盹
I just put him down for a nap.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, buddy.
嘿
Hey.
妈咪
Hi, mommy.
Aaron
Hi  Aaron